# SUCHINLIN

User Experience Designer



#### **PROFILE**

A bit about me and my "why" to designing:

I love helping people. Whether it's through projects or even something as simple as a passing greeting, I enjoy uplifting spirits and lightening loads. It's what brought me into nursing and now to user experience design.

Apart from design, I also am an avid runner and enjoy the discipline, expression, and community that comes with it.

# **SKILLS**

Design Tools	Soft Skills
Figma	Empathy
Sketch	Compassion
Invision	Creativity
Procreate	Leadership

# **UX Skills**

- User Research
- Competitive Research
- Comparative Research
- Persona
- Sketching
- Storyboarding
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Interaction Design
- Usability Testing

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **POLLTAB**

# **UX/UI** Designer

Feb 2021 to Present

- Analyzed heuristic integrity of client's website desktop and mobile
- Conducted research on 5 competitors and 2 comparators
- Fulfilled client's requests to make users' flow more intuitive and UI more "modern" with 3 key UI design changes updated CTA buttons, imagery, and color-scheme
- Crafted new style guide and logo for brand redesign using Figma

# PERSONAL PORTFOLIO DESIGN

# **UX/UI** Designer

May 2020 to Present

- Collaborated with engineer to launch 2 variations of portfolio
- Developed and designed style guidelines (typography, color scheme, and components) and high fidelity prototypes on Figma
- Created personalized icons for portfolio use using Figma

#### MAKE AMERICA DINNER AGAIN

#### **UX Design Consultant**

April 2020

- Spearheaded team of 3 with focus on MVP
- Conducted and synthesized research to guide design decisions
  6 email interviews, 20 responses to custom-made survey, and
  149 responses from client's existing survey
- Ideated design solutions for low to mid fidelity prototype
- Pitched project outcomes and compiled all deliverables for client

#### **GENERAL ASSEMBLY**

# **UX Design Apprentice**

Jan - April 2020

- Certified completion of 400 hours of instruction
- Completed 3 solo design projects and 3 team design projects for both mobile and desktop 4 UX/Research, 2 UI predominant

MOUNT SINAI BETH ISRAEL, Cardiac Tele / Stroke Unit

# Registered Nurse, Unit Team Lead

Nov 2009 - July 2019

- Redesigned information boards and patient data collection forms
- Researched uptodate practices for policy and procedure committee
- Led team of 14 nurses and support staff through 12 hr day shifts

# **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly** 

UX Design Immersive Jan - Apr 2020

**General Assembly** 

Visual Design Workshop

May 2020

**New York University** 

B.S. Nursing Sept 2005 - May 2009

**Udemy** 

Drawing and Painting with Procreate May 2021